(Sheldon:)And Pythagoras had
(Sheldon:)an irrational fear of beans.
(Sheldon:)Tesla fell madly in love
with a pigeon
(Sheldon:)who he claimed loved him back.
(Penny:)Maybe he just had bread
in his pocket.
(Sheldon:)The list extends
outside of science.
(Sheldon:)Painters like Van Gogh
and Pollock,
(Sheldon:)chess champion Bobby Fischer,
(Sheldon:)Brian Wilson of the Beach Boy...
(upbeat pop melody playing)
♪ ...Know if words could say ♪
♪ But darlin',
I'll find a way... ♪
I remember the song!
(Sheldon:)It's called
"Darlin'" by the Beach Boys!
Oh, thank goodness!
I'm not crazy!
(Sheldon:)I don't have
to take a pigeon as my bride!
(Leonard:)There goes our shot at
him living on the roof.
(Raj:)So, all right, there he is.
(Raj:)So, should we
introduce ourselves?
No! Let him spot us.